l2e-global.com 2017-12-26

# E-Global - worldwide Lineage 2 project. Off-like sources - Interlude, Gracia Final, High Five, Classic.

Word from E-Global E-Global has a strong commitment to providing superior service to all of our customers and visitors of this Website and particularly respecting your concerns about privacy. We understand that you may have questions about how this Website collects and uses information and we have prepared this statement to inform you of the privacy principles that govern the Website (the "Privacy Policy"). We will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information or a list of our customers to third parties for their marketing purposes without your explicit consent. Please read this privacy policy to learn more about the ways in which we use and protect your personal information. We want you to fully understand our privacy practices. The privacy practices of this statement apply to our services available under the domain and subdomains of this website (the ‘Site’). By visiting this website you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree please do not use or access our Site. This Privacy Policy describes the information, as part of the normal operation of our services, we collect from you and what may happen to that information. Although this policy may seem long, we have prepared a detailed policy because we believe you should know as much as possible about our practices so that you can make informed decisions. By accepting the Privacy Policy and any other agreement presented to you on the Site, you expressly consent to our use and disclosure of your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Merchant business address: Khelvachauri Aigis st., Batumi Adjara, Georgia 

Contact e-mail: (GlobalWay@gmail.com)

Contact phone number: (+79650633447)

Company's registration name: Natural Divine Georgia LLC

Company's place of registration: Georgia

Company's registered office address: Khelvachauri Aigis st., Batumi Adjara, Georgia

Company's registered number: 448389967
